Hi, in this segment we're going to do another type of a foot brush.
We call this one the Tommy kick or the Tommy brush because he's basically the guy who does it the best and it kind of got named after him.
And what we're going to do it's, this one for me a clockwise spin.
So clockwise spin here and then I'm going to look at the bottom of the Frisbee again.
I'm going to bring my foot up and I'm going to hit it with the outside of my foot bringing it back here.
Swinging it across the Frisbee so it comes back up this way.
So clock spin here, here.
Try that again.
Clock spin set it up here.
You can go into a lot of different moves after that Tommy kick.
It's a great way to save a Frisbee or to pass a Frisbee or to get the Frisbee into another different part of your combination.
So we'll try that one, one more time you go to clock spin.
You'll set it up swing your foot across.
The Tommy kick.